Have your life and eat it too.
Cake is a comedy, romance film directed by Nisha Ganatra.
A travel writer improves her love life when she becomes an
editor for her father's wedding magazine.
Pippa McGee, played by Heather Graham.
Ian, played by David Sutcliffe.
Hemingway Jones, played by Taye Diggs.
Jane, played by Sarah Chalke.
Roxanne, played by Cheryl Hines.
Frank, played by Keram Malicki-Sánchez.
Cake is a 2005 romantic comedy film directed by Nisha Ganatra.
It was released on December 2, 2005 in Canada and is
rated R for language and sexual content.
It stars Heather Graham as Pippa, David Sutcliffe as
Ian, and Taye Diggs as Hemingway.
The film explores themes of dysfunctional family, interracial
romance, wedding, duringcreditsstinger, magazine editor.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.